fuckermate.com 2019-03-31

# Fuckermate

We are committed to protecting your privacy. The following information is designed to help you understand how we collect, use, disseminate and safeguard the information you provide to us while accessing and using our Site. By accessing and using our Site, you signify your assent to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with our information practices, please do not access or use our Site. As provided below, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, add or remove portions of this policy at any time by posting such changes to this page. Such changes will be effective upon posting. 

  1. COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION. We are the sole owner of the information collected on the Site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. We collect information from our users at several different points throughout our Site.

  2. REGISTRATION AND ORDER FORMS. In addition, in order to purchase goods and services from our Site, or to become a member of our Site, a user must complete the on-line registration/order form. During registration, a user is required to provide us with certain contact information (which may include your name, mailing address, phone number, fax number, and e-mail address) and certain financial information (like your credit card number and the expiration date for your credit card). This information is used to set-up and maintain an account, verify credit card details, validate credit identity and to ship product. If we have trouble processing an order or otherwise need to contact a user, the contact information is used to get in touch with the user. From time to time, we may also ask that you provide us with additional information so that we can better tailor our services to meet your needs.

  3. COOKIES. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our Site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For instance, by setting a cookie on our Site, we are able track IP addresses and browser preferences in order to enhance and personalize your experience at our Site. We may also use cookies in order to track referral Site in order to properly compensate our affiliates. Please note that some of our business partners may also use cookies on our Site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

  4. SHARING. We may share aggregate demographic information with our sponsors. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We may also use an outside company or companies to process payments or to fulfill orders. From time to time, we may contract with another party to provide certain specific services to our users. If we have collected your personally identifiable information from one Site, that Site may share the information with other Site within our network in order to provide you with additional goods and services for which we believe you may be interested.  
Except as provided above, we do not currently sell or otherwise make available personally identifiable information about our users to third parties. Nevertheless, we reserve the right to make such information available to third parties in the future in order to enhance and personalize our services, or in the case of bankruptcy, sale of an asset, business or division, a merger or acquisition, or similar change of ownership.

  5. LAW ENFORCEMENT. We will cooperate with law enforcement authorities, private-party litigants, and others seeking information about our end users to the extent required by applicable law. We will also notify the appropriate authorities if we suspect that any of our users are engaged in illegal activities, such as obscenity or child pornography.

  6. LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES. In this Site you could find links that redirect to other websites. Please note that this Privacy Policy does not cover those third party websites the links redirect to. Those websites are not governed by this Privacy Policy and if you have questions about how those specific websites use your information, you’ll need to check those website’s privacy statement.

  7. SECURITY. We agree to use commercially reasonable efforts to protect the information you have provided to us from unauthorized access by using encryption and other security measures. We encourage you to contact us if you are interested in learning more about our security measures.

  8. THIRD PARTY SOURCES OF INFORMATION. From time to time and in order to enhance our services, we may supplement the information we receive from you with information we obtain from third party sources.

  9. CHILDREN. Our Site is not intended for children. Our Site do not target children, nor do we solicit data, or knowingly collect personally identifiable information from them. We encourage parents and legal guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate in the interactive activities offered on the Site their children visit.

  10. CORRECTION/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION. If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as e-mail address or phone number), or if a user no longer desires our service, you may contact us to correct or update this information.

  11. NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting such changes on our Site. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective upon posting such changes. If you access or use any of our Site, you are required to periodically check our Privacy Policy for any changes. If you continue to access or use any of our Site after we have changed our Privacy Policy, you manifest your assent to the changes to our Privacy Policy.  
If we decide to use your personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated in the Privacy Policy at the time that such information was collected, we will attempt to notify you of such changes. You agree that if we send you an e-mail to the e-mail address reflected in our records, such e-mail will constitute acceptable notice to you of the change in our policy. The notice will provide you with an opportunity to "opt-out" so that we may not use your personally identifiable information in a manner which is different from the manner described at the time that you provided us with such information. If you do not affirmatively "opt-out" pursuant to the instructions provided to you in the notice, then you agree that we may use your personally identifiable information in the manner described in the notice. (If we have no e-mail address for you, or if we do not have a current e-mail address for you, then you agree that adequate notice of the change in our policy will be effected by posting such a change onto our Privacy Policy, which shall also disclose information about how you may "opt-out" so that we may not use your personally identifiable information in a manner which is materially different from the manner described at the time that you provided us with such information. If you do not affirmatively "opt-out" pursuant to the instructions posted within the time period specified, then you agree that we may use your personally identifiable information as described in the posted notice).

  12. CONTACT INFORMATION. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or if you need to contact us regarding your personally identifiable information, please send e-mail us at info@fuckermate.com, providing your username or Member ID. We will answer you as soon as possible.

* * *
